<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Log on The Great Garage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Log on The Great Garage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/log/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Changes of The Great Garage 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tgg-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tgg-update-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wish all my readers a happy new year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made a personal page for myself and put it under the &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgao.net&#34;&gt;root&lt;/a&gt; of hgao.net. I have considered to move the blog under blog.hgao.net, but it seems that I&amp;rsquo;ll lose all my links and comments (though only a few at all). Thus, the previous index page is moved under &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgao.net/all&#34;&gt;hgao.net/all&lt;/a&gt;. The new homepage uses prologue theme designed by &lt;a href=&#34;http://html5up.net&#34;&gt;HTML5 UP&lt;/a&gt;, which I think is more suitable for introducing myself at first glance. By saying &amp;ldquo;at first glance&amp;rdquo;, I mean I&amp;rsquo;ll modify it in the following days. In sum, &lt;em&gt;The Great Garage&lt;/em&gt; is not only a blog, but also my representation now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the last six months, I did some practice on LeetCode. A large portion of my articles are about my solution to them, which I don&amp;rsquo;t think worth reading, to be honest. Now I archived them together under &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgao.net/collection/leetcode&#34;&gt;collection&lt;/a&gt;, so each problem can be easily found either by the ID or their titles, and these articles won&amp;rsquo;t appear in the timeline. I also make a collection of my book reviews in another &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgao.net/collection/readings/&#34;&gt;collection&lt;/a&gt;. Here you (and I) can clearly see the metadata and my rate of the books. Thanks to Jekyll, I can add customized metadata to every post, such as problem number, author or my rate. It enables me to extract information from them and demonstrate on the collection page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, my ClustrMaps always shows on the bottom of the page, disregarding the &lt;code&gt;display:none&lt;/code&gt; sentence in the tag. Now I removed it. But I&amp;rsquo;m still wondering what&amp;rsquo;s the proper way to embed these analytical tools. Visits of every pages should be recorded, but I just want the map to show on &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgao.net/about&#34;&gt;About&lt;/a&gt; page. Is it correct to hide the map on other pages?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last thing is, some of comments are lost and I&amp;rsquo;ll try to find them back on Disqus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
